export const WHAT_IS_NOT_WORKING_CONTENT = [
  {
    title: "Cursor",
    icon: "/new-project/cursor-icon.webp",
    colorfulIcon: "/new-project/cursor-icon.webp",
    width: 37,
    height: 37,
    problems_and_solutions: [
      {
        problem:
          "Cursor AI sometimes adds code in the wrong place or creates duplicate files.",
        solution:
          "We run a full code audit to clean up misplaced or duplicate code and restructure it.",
      },
      {
        problem: "On large projects, it slows down and becomes less reliable.",
        solution:
          "We improve your codebase for speed, reliability, and growth.",
      },
      {
        problem:
          "Users faced UI glitches like disappearing “Apply” buttons, etc.",
        solution: "We debug interface issues and fix broken components.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: "Bolt.new",
    icon: "/new-project/bolt-ai-icon.webp",
    colorfulIcon: "/new-project/bolt-ai-icon.webp",
    width: 40,
    height: 37,
    problems_and_solutions: [
      {
        problem:
          "Fixing errors in Bolt Ai often takes millions of tokens, making even small changes expensive.",
        solution:
          "We replace AI assisted coding with expert intervention, reducing costs and making fixes sustainable.",
      },
      {
        problem:
          "Fixing one part in Bolt Ai can accidentally break other working parts of the project.",
        solution:
          "Our approach ensures changes are stable, preventing new issues while fixing existing ones.",
      },
      {
        problem:
          "Bolt Ai is Good for simple prototypes, but struggles with larger or more advanced apps.",
        solution:
          "We upgrade AI based coding builds and make them ready for the market.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: "Loveable",
    icon: "/new-project/lovable-icon.webp",
    colorfulIcon: "/new-project/lovable-colorful-icon.webp",
    width: 52,
    height: 37,
    problems_and_solutions: [
      {
        problem:
          "Lovable works fine for small MVPs, but breaks when projects get bigger or more advanced.",
        solution:
          "We restructure the architecture with our project recovery services for stable performance.",
      },
      {
        problem:
          "It generates bloated or inconsistent code, which often needs manual cleanup.",
        solution:
          "We perform a thorough code audit and then code rescue to clean and optimize.",
      },
      {
        problem:
          "Frequent bug fixes and retries make Loveable costly for bigger projects.",
        solution:
          "We resolve underlying issues, preventing repeated fixes and lowering overall project costs.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: "FlutterFlow",
    icon: "/new-project/flutter-flow-icon.webp",
    colorfulIcon: "/new-project/flutter-flow-colorful-icon.webp",
    width: 30,
    height: 37,
    problems_and_solutions: [
      {
        problem:
          "The auto-generated Flutter code can be messy, making handoff to developers difficult.",
        solution: "We restructure auto‑generated code, making handoffs smooth.",
      },
      {
        problem:
          "Creating apps with Flutterflow that work fully offline is tricky without deep customization.",
        solution:
          "Our team adds the custom backend logic and offline capabilities FlutterFlow lacks, making your app functional.",
      },
      {
        problem:
          "Many features rely on templates; customizing beyond them often needs manual coding.",
        solution:
          "We go beyond templates with customized development, adding unique features.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: "Google Firebase",
    icon: "/new-project/google-firebase-icon.webp",
    colorfulIcon: "/new-project/google-firebase-colorful-icon.webp",
    width: 32,
    height: 37,
    problems_and_solutions: [
      {
        problem:
          "The costs for database reads/writes, storage, and bandwidth grow with the project.",
        solution:
          "We optimize database structure and reduce unnecessary reads/writes to keep Google Firebase costs predictable and manageable.",
      },
      {
        problem:
          "Google Firebase doesn’t support complex queries like SQL joins or deep filtering.",
        solution:
          "We implement custom backend services or hybrid solutions, extending Firebase’s capabilities for complex data handling.",
      },
      {
        problem:
          "Storing user data on Google’s servers can raise challenges for GDPR or region-specific compliance.",
        solution:
          "Our team design compliant data strategies, including regional hosting or external integrations, ensuring your app meets GDPR and local regulations.",
      },
    ],
  },
];
